<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JFrog Platform Setup on JFrog Platform on Azure Workshop</title>
    <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in JFrog Platform Setup on JFrog Platform on Azure Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get a Free JFrog Platform Instance</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/421_jfrog_free.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/421_jfrog_free.html</guid>
      <description>If you do not have access to a JFrog Platform instance, use the JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier to get your own JFrog Platform instance with Artifactory, Xray and Pipelines.
When signing up for the JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier, ensure that you select Azure and the region for your resource group.
  JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activate JFrog Pipelines CI/CD</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/422_jfrog_pipelines.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/422_jfrog_pipelines.html</guid>
      <description>Go to your JFrog Platform instance at https://[server name].jfrog.io. Refer to your JFrog Free Subscription Activation email if needed. Substitute your server name.   Login to your JFrog Platform instance with your credentials.   Once logged into your JFrog Platform instance, you will be presented with the landing page.   Go to Application &amp;gt; Pipelines and follow the instructions to activate JFrog Pipelines. This will take a few minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Docker Repositories</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/423_docker_repositories.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/423_docker_repositories.html</guid>
      <description>In your JFrog Platform instance at the top right, enable the drop down menu and select Quick Setup.  On the Create Repositories dialog, choose Docker and click Next.   Next, enter workshop for the Repositories Prefix.
  Click Create. This will create the following docker repositories:
   workshop-docker-local workshop-docker-remote workshop-docker   Local repositories are physical, locally-managed repositories into which you can deploy artifacts. These are repositories that are local to the JFrog Artifactory instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Xray Security</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/424_xray_setup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/424_xray_setup.html</guid>
      <description>In your JFrog Platform instance, go to Administration &amp;gt; Xray &amp;gt; Watches &amp;amp; Policies.   Click Create a Policy.
  Call the security policy, High-Severity.
   Click on New Rule.
  Name the rule High-Severity and select High for the Minimal Severity. Click Save.
   Click Create to create this new security policy.
  Click on the Watches tab under Watches &amp;amp; Policies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
