<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Setup on JFrog Platform on Azure Workshop</title>
    <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Setup on JFrog Platform on Azure Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JFrog Azure Event: Get an Azure Environment</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/412_azure_event_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/412_azure_event_account.html</guid>
      <description>Only complete this section if you are running the workshop through an JFrog Azure hosted event. If you are not at a JFrog Azure hosted event, go here.
 For an JFrog Azure hosted event, you will be provided with a registration link and an activation code. The following steps show how to use the activation code to access an Azure environment for this workshop.
 Go to the registration link in your browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-paced: Create an Azure account</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/413_self_paced_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/413_self_paced_account.html</guid>
      <description>Only complete this section if you are running the workshop on your own. If you are at an JFrog Azure hosted event, go here.
   If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have an Azure account, create one now by going here.
  Select Start free.
  Sign in with your Microsoft or GitHub account or create a free Microsoft account.
  On the About you page, select your correct country or region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up your Azure Cloud Shell</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/414_azure_cloud_shell.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/414_azure_cloud_shell.html</guid>
      <description>Azure Cloud Shell is an interactive, authenticated, browser-accessible shell for managing Azure resources.
 In your Azure Portal, click the Azure Cloud Shell button.  You will be prompted for a shell type. Choose Bash.  If this is your first time using Azure Cloud Shell, you will be prompted to create storage to support it. Go ahead and do this by clicking Create storage with the provided subscription. It will take a few minutes to set up the storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an AKS Cluster</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/415_create_cluster.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/415_create_cluster.html</guid>
      <description>Before creating an AKS cluster for our application, we must first set up the required networking with the following steps.
 Now we are ready to create an AKS cluster. In your Azure Cloud Shell, let&amp;rsquo;s get the latest version of Kubernetes that is available with the following command.  VERSION=$(az aks get-versions \ --location $REGION \ --query &#39;orchestrators[?!isPreview] | [-1].orchestratorVersion&#39; \ --output tsv) echo $VERSION Let&amp;rsquo;s create an environment variable for the cluster name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the Workshop Code</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/416_workshop_code.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/azure-aks-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_azure_setup/416_workshop_code.html</guid>
      <description>The workshop code is located at https://github.com/jfrogtraining/azure-aks-workshop GitHub repository. We will fork and clone this repository in order to pull the required workshop files and scripts.
 Go to https://github.com/jfrogtraining/azure-aks-workshop and fork this repository to your GitHub account.  Clone the repo. You can do this locally in the Azure Cloud Shell. You can open another Azure Cloud Shell session.  git clone https://github.com/&amp;lt;your user name&amp;gt;/azure-aks-workshop.git
Set your GitHub username and email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
